Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride
away, we're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun,
while our dreams are never ending.
So let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake
up, heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our minds will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop
it We will be one, go ahead
Back in the old days,
way before your time Garp was
considered the devil incarnate to
all pirates They say time heals
all wounds But decades have passed,
and my pain still remains. Speak up!
Is all that true?
No, of course not!
I didn't hear him right!
My name is definitely Luffy!
Then why did you answer
when he called you Luffy?
Seeing as you're Garp's grandson, I'm afraid
you're gonna have to pay for his sins!
Take it up with Grandpa, why don't ya?
Hold on, so you two are related!
I call everyone Grandpa!
If you truly are the
notorious Straw Hat Luffy,
I'll cut you down where you stand!
You know what the real shame is.
If only I'd found out about
Garp's son, Dragon, sooner.
I could have prevented you from
being born in the first place.
Whoa, what's going on?
Seems Don Jinjiao's starting to brawl.
You can't be serious.
Let's slow down and talk about this.
I'm gonna rip that ridiculous beard off.
It took me years to grow.
The Don is getting back up.
Is he going to attack again?
I don't know how much old age has affected
him, but in his prime, the bounty on him.
ran over a half a billion berries.
Stay out of my way, Don Xin Zhao.
Because if you don't, I'm
afraid things will get ugly.
Cavendish is drawing his sword on him?
Look at that.
What?
One of the finest blades
in the world, Durandal!
Worry this, head arms!
Beautiful sword, blue bones!
Cavendish is gonna cut
through his skull! No way!
They're equally matched!
Jolando can't stab him.
That big guy's head is
tougher than a sword.
And the other guy's holding
him off with one arm.
Both of them are scary.
Looks like he's not going to stop.
Unless I fight back at full power.
He's getting old.
Almost as old as you.
Did he just KO'd Qin Zhao?
Who the hell is that little bearded guy?
What a walloping.
What?
It had no effect?
Maybe all the legends about
him are actually true.
They say with one headbutt, Qin Zhao
split the ice continent in half.
The whole stinking continent!
I wasn't holding back on that punch,
But the old man got right back up.
Well, isn't this a nice surprise?
You two have talent.
But sadly, it won't be enough
to save you from my wrath.
There's one thing I know for certain.
Based on your strength, your Straw Hat.
Give it a rest, right?
You're the grandson of a demon.
You steal popularity from others.
All you seem to do is attract iron.
Neither of those things is my fault, you
got it, and my name's Lucy by the way,
if you had as much brains as looks,
you'd stay out of my way,
Cavendish or I'll kill you too!
That's enough, Gramps.
Have you lost your damn mind?
You're trying to get us disqualified—it's
Zion boo from the Kano kingdom!
You'll
unhand your grandfather this instant!
Not a chance!
Whatever's going on, stop it!
I found Garp's grandson, my enemy!
Right here!
Remember why we're here!
If we're eliminated, we can't
fulfill our real purpose!
Cool it!
You guys over there had better not
be doing what I think you're doing!
Any fighting outside the
arena results in ejection!
Those
are Coliseum guards!
I'm gonna settle the score right now!
now Elimination be damned!
Where the hell did he go?
Don't worry.
That fake bearded guy's in Block C.
We'll see him again in the Coliseum.
So if you want to kill him,
just wait until the fight.
I'm not going to let
you escape, Straw Hat!
I will find you!
You'll be dead before you
set foot in that arena!
Look at the mess they left.
What was that all about anyway?
I thought I heard someone say Straw Hat.
You thought or you're sure?
They could have been talking
about the pirate Luffy.
You think he entered?
Nah, there's no way.
Well, this is bad.
I was trying to lay low too.
There goes my promise to Franky.
There are only about 70
competitors still left in the ring!
The military captain of Dressrosa's
self-defense army has been eliminated!
Another victim of the sinister
pair, Abdullah and Jeet!
They should be disqualified
for dirty tricks!
The tank can't be out yet!
And with that, over a hundred
gladiators have fallen!
There are barely thirty
left standing in the ring!
Not much longer now.
No matter how tough the remaining
competition is, we have the King Punch!
Which one of you wants to go first?
For those of you who wish
to bleed, step forward.
Abdullah and Jeet, that vicious duo,
have mercilessly taken
down the strongman, Lepant.
Make a bleed, Delvin!
So cruel, so vicious.
Look these words up in the dictionary and
you'll surely find a
picture of this man's face.
On the other side of the stage,
a duel has erupted between
Jiao Kung Do martial
artist Blue Gilly and
the mysterious gladiator.
Ricky, which of these bruisers
will emerge victorious?
Have you been watching how
tough that fish dude is?
He knocked out all his
opponents in a single blow!
Yes!
Damn, I hope he wins!
Somebody stop him!
I don't believe my eyes!
Is there no depth to which
Bartolomeo will sink?
How low will he go?
Why isn't anybody kicking his ass?
In plain view of this arena,
without any discretion,
he's pulled out his unspeakable bits.
and is relieving himself in the mount!
The most indecent act ever performed
in the history of this coliseum!
That's what I'm talking about.
Feels so good.
He's desecrating a place of bloodshed!
Someone do something!
Yes! Finally!
I'm not too proud to strike you from
behind if you won't take this seriously.
You better finish with that quickly.
You degenerate.
Hey!
Come on, man.
I'm the fence is here with my wiener out.
The hero that has answered our
plea is the fishman warrior, Hack!
Four thousand brick.
Now's your chance!
Kick this guy's ass, Hack! Fish!
Gotcha!
What's going on?
Why is Hack the one on the ground?
Battle-O-Mail didn't flinch!
That's crazy.
What's going on?
Who or what is this lewd, crude contender?
Surely some kind of monster!
Hack is defeated!
It looked like he didn't
even get near him!
What did Bartolomeo do just now?
Ah, no, I was rooting for Hack!
Someone put an end to that
obnoxious little jackass!
Aren't you supposed to be impartial?
It looks like it's anybody's
game at this point.
B-blocks down to 24 competitors.
About time to wrap this thing up.
That guy will be fun to kill. Come on!
It's heating up here.
Comes the moment we planned for.
Even the most accomplished
fighters are dropping
like flies—not just Hack
but the unknown gladiator!
Ricky is down for the count as well.
Blue Ghillie is on a roll!
roll
Did you really think you could cut
anything with a doflate like that, old man?
In the end, my old age was what bested me.
I hate his cheering for bloodshed,
but even more so, I hate you,
Doflamingo.
Dogama had the right idea, huh?
This competition is really thinning out.
Oh, yeah.
Most of the other guys are long gone.
I'm glad we teamed up, or I would be, too.
Wait for the cue from Dogama.
That means it's time to break.
Then we'll fight amongst
ourselves until somebody wins.
You got that?
There's still a few guys left standing.
Here we go.
Let's eliminate Blue Gilly while
we're all still working together.
AHHHHH!!!!
AHHHH!!!
AHHHHHHH!!!
Dogma? Gamma?
Like a pack of dogs!
Loyal, but not too bright!
What the...
You were supposed to give a signal!
You lied!
TRAINOR!
What?
I'm sorry, fellas.
It's nothing personal.
I'm just following orders, same as you.
Does that mean you were in on this, too?
You were gonna use and get
rid of us from the very start!
And you're too greedy for your own good!
Let's see if you live long
enough to collect your pay!
You're a monster!
Warriors who can't think for themselves
end up doing someone else's dirty work.
I'll let you take care
of the rest, Longleg.
But you've made a fatal mistake at
turning your back to me, Bluekilly.
Bye.
How dare you betray me, Bluekilly!
Dagobah, the tactician, is defeated!
That's what I'm talking about!
Oh, thank you, Kelly!
That guy couldn't have
been any more suspicious.
I'm surprised anyone here
was willing to trust him.
Hold on!
What's happening now?
Bellamy's down, but he's the
one who went in for the attack!
How does Bartolomeo keep doing this?
No, it can't be!
Sorry, folks, I think Bellamy's done for!
What was that?
What the hell kind of
Devil Fruit did you eat?
They beat him without even moving.
Just like what he did to Hack earlier!
But how did he do that?
Crazy You can do it!
Keep banging in there!
So, Isabella, what do you plan to do?
I mean, what good's a king without
any loyal subjects to rule over?
I mean, everyone in this arena
wants to be the one to do you in.
Dagoma served his purpose well.
My punch is warmed up.
All that's left is to throw it.
Nothing is more dangerous
than an unchecked weapon.
That formation wasn't
protecting me from you.
It was protecting you from me.
Don't think so?
Wait and see.
Dude, I just thought of
something. What is it?
That's the King of Prodents, right?
I've heard about that guy.
They said he destroyed an entire
enemy fort with a single punch.
Nah, that's crazy.
I'm sure he had a cannon
or something. It's true.
Rumor has it that punch is powerful
enough to defeat one of the four emperors.
What?
My point is, if that story's legit,
then everybody on this side of the
Coliseum's gonna be blown away by the impact!
Huh?
Come on, man, nobody can punch that hard!
I don't know, guys.
I remember hearing that story, too.
This is bad!
If he throws a punch like that,
hundreds of people will die for sure!
the tension is palpable now after quietly
keeping that punch in
reserve it looks like the
king's ready to strike
mark
my words
i will win
the flame flame fruit for
the kingdom of produce
this does not look good he's gonna do
it here he comes we should run hurry
Maybe the rumors were true.
If so, we're in trouble.
Oh, well, not giving up, huh?
Get your stupid spring off of me.
You're about to find out you
messed with the wrong guy.
King!
Now's my chance to kill him! Move it!
Shooting hard!
What is that?
That...
That was incredible!
No one in the ring could
have survived that blow!
Elisabello has wiped out all of his
competition with a single punch!
I wouldn't want to be on the
wrong side of that punch!
There you have it, folks!
Bellamy, Blue Gilly, and all the
other fighters have been eliminated!
Out of all 138 competitors in Block B,
I hereby proclaim the
victor to be King Elizabeth!
Is somebody still down there?
That means the fight's not over!
Good thing he was facing
that side when he punched.
We're all safe over here.
it's a barrier what's
wrong can't create a wall
by crossing your fingers
like this come on it's so
easy a little kid could
do it well guess it could
be because I ate the berry
berry fruit barrier crash
the fighting king elizabello is out of
the running that means block b's winner is
now that that's out of the way
the rest of you can go to hell too
Screw you, dude!
Yeah, buzz off!
No way!
The winner was that weird chicken, dude?
The flame flame fruit's mine,
and soon I can give it to you.
Huh? You too?
You are your voice.
Somebody could hear you.
So you're telling me you want
to destroy the Smile Factory?
Correct.
My comrades and I have been making
preparations to do just that.
Then tell me where it is.
I'll tear that factory down in no time.
You can't do that.
Yeah, why not?
If you do, then it'll be too late for
us to rescue all of the factory workers.
It's a risky mission.
The fate of this country depends
on whether or not we succeed.
Indeed.
My friend, if you truly have enough
courage to stand against Doflamingo,
then first let me tell you
the sad history of Dressrosa.